parkingpanda.com 2018-12-27

# Privacy Policy - Parking Panda

Parking Panda Corp. (" _we_ ", " _our_ " or " _us_ ") believes in your privacy and sharing opinions on www.parkingpanda.com (the " _Site_ "). Our lawyers drafted this privacy policy to protect the collection, use and disclosure of your information on the Site and the services, features, content or applications we offer (together with the Site, the _“Services”_ ). Please read it! This way you’ll know how we collect and use your information and share it with third parties. If you use our Site, then you are agreeing to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage disclosure and any other things we do with your information.

Please read it! This way you’ll know how we collect and use your information and share it with third parties. If you use our Site, then you are agreeing to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage disclosure and any other things we do with your information. 

_What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?_

This Privacy Policy covers the treatment of personally identifiable information ( _"Personal Information"_ ) gathered when you use or access the Service _and_ Personal Information that our business partners share with us or that we share with them. [You may create a user account by using Facebook Connect, Twitter, Foursquare or LinkedIn] ( _“Account”_ ) to access the Services. [We don’t own or control Facebook, Foursquare LinkedIn, Twitter or] other third party websites, services or applications ( _“Third Party Services”_ ), so don’t blame us for the content or privacy policies of those Third Party Services. You should review their privacy policies and terms so that you know what you’re getting into. 

_Information we Collect_

We may request, collect and/or display some of your Personal Information when using the Services. It helps us make the Site better, send you Information, improve content, operate the Services, offer promotions, and customize ads. 

_Account Information_

When you create an Account, you will provide Information that could be Personal Information, such as the following: 

_Parking Space Owners_  
Name  
Physical Address  
Phone Number (preferably a mobile phone capable of receiving text messages)   
Email Address  
PayPal or bank account information (processed via third parties – please see below for more information)  
Photo or Google Street View of the parking space listed   
Feedback on renters   

_Parking Space Renters_  
Name  
Mobile Phone Number (text message functions must be enabled)  
PayPal, bank account or credit card information (processed via third parties – please see below for more information)  
Vehicle license plate number & vehicle make, model, color and year  
Feedback on parking space owners  

Personal Information also includes your [Facebook, Twitter, Foursquare or LinkedIn] log-in credentials, password, transactional information based upon your activity on the Site (information we need to get paid and to pay you), user feedback and comments, demographic information, and authentication information. Some of this information is mandatory and some is optional. For example, we need to locate your address for the parking space and locate you in real-time if you are driving around looking for a parking space so that we can make recommendations to you for the nearest parking spot. We will track the parking transactions in real-time and have this data visible on our site through the use of Google Maps. We may also receive other information directly from Third Party Services, such as your name, profile photo or avatar, job title. [If you give us permission through the account settings, we may also access your Facebook Friends, LinkedIn Connections, and other similar information from Third Party Services.] You acknowledge that this information is your Personal Information and by creating an Account on the Services and providing Personal Information to us, you allow others, including us, to identify you. When you use the Service, we may know your location and you agree that it’s cool for us to contact you, as needed, for such housekeeping matters. 

_Locational information_

They say there are 3 keys to success in real estate: location, location, location. We couldn’t agree more. All of our services are location-based services and thus we collect and store information about your location when you use our service and when you make a space rental transaction. This information can come from a variety of sources depending on the client you use to access the Services; for example, a mobile phone may report its GPS location at the time you access our Site or Services. 

_Financial information_

We do not currently collect financial information, such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information); that information is collected and stored by our third party payment processing company (the _“Payment Processor”_ ), and use and storage of that information is governed by the Payment Processor’s applicable terms of service and privacy policy.

_User Content:_

We love your opinions! We want you to share them with us and other uses to improve the Parking Panda experience. In fact, we ask you to rate parking space owners and renters after the transaction so that we can keep tabs on the people and spaces that are the best. When you do, we get to keep that data indefinitely, even after you terminate your Account. As long as we don’t share your Personal Information with third parties, we may continue to disclose other content to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy. 

_User Supplied Information:_

Sometimes we ask you to complete surveys, answer questions, and provide other information for us or our partners. If you want to answer us, that’s great! If not, that’s totally fine, too. Though in some instances, you may not be able to access the Services if required information is not provided

_IP Address Information and Other Information Collected Automatically:_

  * When you go to our Site, we automatically receive and record Information from your web browser when you interact with the Services, including your IP address, location, browser or mobile platform, cookie information, and page information you requested. 
  * Generally, the usage information is collected and used in the aggregate so that we can make the Services better. We treat this information as non-Personal Information, except where required to do so by applicable law. 

_We send you email and text messages._

In order for us to communicate with you in real-time and most quickly enable a parking space transaction, we need to email and text message you directly. Please be advised that your mobile phone carrier’s text message rates will apply. By using the Service you are giving us permission to send you text messages and emails regarding the transactions you request. We track when you open emails so that we can deliver more interesting emails, keep you entertained, and deliver an out-of-this-world-easy parking rental experience. If you cannot be reached this way, then it will be challenging for you to use the Services. Other than for transactional and Account-related matters, if you don’t want to hear from us, just unsubscribe. (Though we promise to make our informational emails really entertaining!) We will not send you text messages for anything unrelated to the Service you request. 

_Information Collected Using Cookies (not the baked kind):_

  * Here’s the breakdown on digital cookies: (1) they are pieces of text that may be provided to your computer through your web browser when you access a website; (2) your browser stores cookies for each website you visit; (3) we use cookies to enable our servers to recognize your locational data, mobile or web browser, and (4) to tell us how and when you visit the Site and otherwise use the Services through the Internet. 
  * Our cookies don’t, by themselves, contain Personal Information. We use cookies to identify that your web browser has accessed aspects of the Services and may associate that information with your Account (if you have one). 
  * Most browsers have an option to turn off the cookie feature, which prevents your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie. We recommend that you leave cookies active, as they enable you to take advantage of the coolest features of the Services. It’s up to you. 
  * Our ad partners may deliver cookies to provide targeted ads to you. Our Privacy Policy just covers what we do – not third parties who put cookies on your computer or their data usage. You can opt out, but it may limit the Services. 

_Information Related to Ads and the Use of Web Beacons:_

  * Third party ads may contribute to your Parking Panda fun, so we may serve ‘em up to you on the Site. 
  * Sometimes the ads are targeted to particular users, sometimes they are based on Personal Information (i.e. location, gender), Services usage patterns of particular users, or your activity on Third Party Services. Sometimes ads are anonymized. 
  * We like our ads to be effective, so we may deliver a file (known as a “web beacon”) from an ad network to you through the Services. Web beacons allow ad networks to deliver targeted ads and to provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for us and for advertisers, aka better data. Because your mobile or web browser must request these ads and web beacons from the ad network’s servers, these companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site.

_Aggregate Information:_

We love data! Let’s be honest, most of the internet is about data. It helps us improve our products and make our Site and the services better. We collect statistical Information about how both unregistered and Account users, collectively, use the Services ( _“Aggregate Information”_ ). Some of this Information is derived from Personal Information. However, statistical Information is not Personal Information and can’t be tied back to you, your Account or your web browser. Certain non-Personal Information could become Personal Information is aggregated with other pieces of data in a way that enables you to be identifiable. We may at times combine non-personal information with Personal Information to better deliver the Services and special offers and ads to you and also to better understand how our Site and the Services are used. In the event that such data is combined, it will not be shared with third parties. 

_Who do you share my information with?_

The services are designed to help you share Information with others, provide you with great content, and have a few chuckles! Sometimes we share information with third parties to accomplish these goals. 

_IP Address Information:_

We collect and store IP address Information, but it’s not made public. Sometimes we share this Information with our partners, service providers and other persons with whom we conduct business, as stated herein. 

_Financial Information_

As stated above, we do not currently collect financial information, as that information is collected and stored by our Payment Processor. However, we may from time to time request and receive some of your financial information from our Payment Processor for the purposes of completing transactions you have initiated through the Services, enrolling you in discount, rebate, and other programs in which you elect to participate, protecting against or identify possible fraudulent transactions, and otherwise as needed to manage our business.

_Information You Elect to Share with us:_

We tell you how we are using the data when you submit it to us, i.e. use of Site features, response to advertisers, information requests, products or services purchases, survey responses, or other purposes. Some of your activity is public by default, i.e. content you publicly post and some profile information. Account holders have this data associated with them. Unregistered users have anonymous information tracked (such as what pages they have visited) through cookies and stored by us. 

If you share Personal Information using certain public features of the Site, or information with us through the use of your Facebook, Foursqure, LinkedIn, Twitter or other Third Party Service (including locational data), other people who see it may share that information without your control or knowledge … so be careful! People will know where you are parked! Be smart about sharing Personal Information through publicly accessible websites and services. 

_Aggregate Information:_

We share Aggregate Information with our partners, service providers and other business partners so they can understand how and how often people use our Services and their services or websites. This facilitates improvements of our Services’ interface with them. In return, these third parties may share aggregate or other non-Personal Information about you that they have independently developed or acquired.

_User Profile Information:_

We share your username with other users and only the other Personal Information that you elect to share in the Account. Please keep in mind that you will need to share Personal Information with other users in order to complete a parking transaction through the Site. 

_Information Shared with our Partners:_

We work closely with other businesses that sometimes sell or promote products to you through our Services. We will clearly state when one of our partners is associated with a transaction, and we will share your Personal Information that is related to such transactions with that business, unless you have opted out of marketing partner communications during Account registration or through your Account settings. 

_Information Shared with our Agents:_

_We employ and contract with people and other entities that perform certain tasks on our behalf and who are under our control (our _“Agents”_ ). We may need to share Personal Information with our Agents in order to provide the Services. Unless we tell you differently, our Agents do not have any right to use Personal Information or other Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information with our Agents._

_Information Disclosed Pursuant to Business Transfers:_

If our business gets acquired, we sell substantially all of our assets, or (gasp!) we go out of business, user Information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that this is ok, and that any acquirer of us or our assets may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

_Information Disclosed for Our Protection and the Protection of Others… (aka, super-legal data usage):_

We also reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any Information as we reasonably believe is necessary to (i) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (ii) enforce these Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations hereof, (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, (iv) respond to user support requests, or (v) protect our rights, property or safety, our users and the public. This includes exchanging Information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and spam/malware prevention.

_Information We Share With Your Consent:_

Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and you will be able to prevent the sharing of this Information.

_Really … Is Information About Me Secure?_

Your Account is password protected for your privacy and security. Please don’t give out your password, and please sign out of public computers when accessing your Account. We try our best to protect your security, but we can’t guarantee it (sorry … hacking happens!). Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. 

_International Users: we process data in the United States & United States’ data protection laws are different_

If you are located outside of the United States, note that the Site is (i) hosted by computer servers in the United States, (ii) processes and stores data in the United States, and (iii) United States federal and state governments, courts, or law enforcement or regulatory agencies may be able to obtain disclosure of your Information through laws applicable in the United States. If you use the Site or Services or share Personal Information with us, then this constitutes your consent to the transfer of your Personal Information outside of your home country, including the United States. 

_Avoid Phishing_

Safeguarding your information is important to us and we appreciate your cooperation in doing the same. Identity theft and “phishing” are rampant and problematic. (For more information about phishing, visit the Federal Trade Commission’s website at [http://www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/).) We will _never_ email you to ask for your password, payment information, credit card, bank account, PayPal account, driver’s license number in a non-secure unsolicited email or phone call. 

_How Do I Access My Information?_

If you created an Account, just login and access it through your Account settings. If not, just delete cookies through your web browser settings.

_For California users: California Privacy Rights:_ Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of personal customer Information which we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact Information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: 3422 Fait Ave Baltimore MD, 21224.

_Can I Delete My Account?_

Yes, it’s totally cool. Just login and delete it through your Account settings. Activity generated prior to deletion will remain stored by us and may be publicly accessible. The fact that you got the money parking spot within a ½ mile walk of the stadium may be retained for posterity. 

_Children’s Privacy_

This Site is not directed to individuals under 13 years old. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from individuals under 13. If you are driving looking for a parking space and you are 13 years old or under, you’ve got bigger problems. 

_Compliance with Law_

We take legal inquiries seriously and we will cooperate with local, state, federal and international governmental authorities to enforce and comply with the law. At our sole discretion, we will disclose any information necessary to comply with the law, respond to claims, and participate in the legal process (including subpoenas) to stop or prevent illegal, unethical or objectionable activity, protect public safety, or protect the property and rights of the Company. 

_What Happens When There Are Changes to this Privacy Policy?_

Life moves pretty fast, so we may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Information we collect is subject to the policy at the time of collection. If we make any changes, we’ll notify you by email or posting a notice on the Site. If you use the Services after the posting date, then you’re bound by the new Privacy Policy. 

_I’ve Got Questions (and May Have Some Concerns)._

If you do, then please email us directly at [hello@parkingpanda.com](mailto:hello@parkingpanda.com). We’ll do our best to resolve it. 

Effective Date: 08/08/2011
